[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How does Nemo disappear in the 2003 animated movie Finding Nemo?", "correct_answer": "A scuba diver catches him.", "incorrect_answers": ["A whale swallows him.", "A seagull takes him away.", "A shark kidnaps him."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are a total of 10 siblings in the talented Wayans family.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The highly successful movie Schindlers List, directed by Steven Spielberg, is based on this historical novel by Australian author Thomas Keneally.", "correct_answer": "Schindlers Ark", "incorrect_answers": ["The Unlikely Hero", "Noahs Ark", "The Lost Ark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the crime team that chases the group throughout the movie The Goonies?", "correct_answer": "The Fratellis", "incorrect_answers": ["The Manatellis", "The Macellis", "The Frangellis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the cougar that rides with Ricky in the movie Talladega Nights?", "correct_answer": "Karen", "incorrect_answers": ["Leroy", "Larry", "Marco"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The best gin rummy players remember every card played.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these objects does Perseus contain?", "correct_answer": "NGC 1499", "incorrect_answers": ["M45", "M101", "PSR 0329+54"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1936 Alan Turing described the a-machine (later renamed Turing Machine) as a device that can simulate the logic of a computer.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Anemometers, from the Greek word anemos meaning wind, can be used to measure this.", "correct_answer": "Winds Pressure and Velocity", "incorrect_answers": ["Winds Moisture and Velocity", "Winds Velocity", "Winds Pressure"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who sang the theme song to the James Bond classic, From Russia With Love?", "correct_answer": "Matt Monroe", "incorrect_answers": ["Neil Sedaka", "Bobby Vinton", "Ricky Nelson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What disease took many lives in Russia, Poland and Romania during World War I ?", "correct_answer": "Typhus", "incorrect_answers": ["Malaria", "Smallpox", "Cholera"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the main ingredient of the Ambrosia salad?", "correct_answer": "Fruits", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Seafood", "Pickles"]}]